const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question: "1. What is the capital of India?",
    options: ["Mumbai", "Delhi", "Kolkata", "Chennai"],
    answer: "Delhi"
  },
  {
    question: "2. Which is the smallest prime number?",
    options: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "3. What does CSS stand for?",
    options: [
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "Colorful Style System",
      "Computer Style Structure",
      "Creative Style Sheets"
    ],
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets"
  },
  {
    question: "4. Which is the longest river in the world?",
    options: ["Amazon", "Yangtze", "Nile", "Ganga"],
    answer: "Nile"
  },
  {
    question: "5. Which gas do plants absorb from the atmosphere?",
    options: ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
    answer: "Carbon Dioxide"
  },
  {
    question: "6. Who invented the telephone?",
    options: [
      "Alexander Graham Bell",
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Thomas Edison"
    ],
    answer: "Alexander Graham Bell"
  },
  {
    question: "7. What is 15 divided by 3?",
    options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: "8. Which animal is known as the Ship of the Desert?",
    options: ["Horse", "Camel", "Donkey", "Elephant"],
    answer: "Camel"
  },
  {
    question: "9. In which direction does the sun rise?",
    options: ["North", "West", "East", "South"],
    answer: "East"
  },
  {
    question: "10. Which of these is a programming language?",
    options: ["HTML", "Python", "CSS", "Photoshop"],
    answer: "Python"
  }
];

export default quizQuestions;
